Guide to the Deep Dish TV Records MSS.312
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series V. Subject Files, 1980-2014; 12.5 Linear Feet in 15 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes; 2.49 Gigabytes in 763 files
  - Media Organizations -- Hallwalls Contemporary Arts Center, 1985-1990 (Box 62, Folder 29, Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Media Organizations -- HDTV Enterprises, 1990 (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Media Organizations -- The Hometown Tube, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Media Organizations -- Human Services Televison Network, 1986 (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Media Organizations -- IDERA Films, 1993 (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Media Organizations -- IMAGW Film/Video Center, 1987-1994 (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Media Organizations -- Independent Film and Video Alliance, 1989-1993 (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Media Organizations -- Independent Focus, 1991-1992 (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Media Organizations -- Independent Media Distributions Alliance, 1991-1993 (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Media Organizations -- Independent Television Service, 1991 (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Media Organizations -- Indymedia, 2001 (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Media Organizations -- Institute for Alternative Journalism, 1995 (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Media Organizations -- Institute for Global Communications, Undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Media Organizations -- Inter-Community Newsletter for Southern Wisconsin, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Media Organizations -- Intermedia Arts, Minnesota, 1990 (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Media Organizations -- International Documentary Association, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Media Organizations -- International Media Resource Exchange, 1992-1994 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Media Organizations -- International Network of Progressive Film and Video, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Media Organizations -- ISKRA, 1976-1981 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Media Organizations -- Jersey Clips, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Media Organizations -- Jones Intercable "Playback" Newsletter, 1986-1989 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Media Organizations --K-SAT Broadcasting, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Media Organizations -- Kyuk Video Productions, 1986-1991 (Box 63, Folder 10, Box 77, Folder 18)
  - Media Organizations -- Labor Link TV, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Media Organizations -- Latin American Video Archives, Undated (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Media Organizations -- Les Films du Village, 1992 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Media Organizations -- Lesbian Gay Television (LGTV), Rhode Island, Undated (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - Media Organizations -- Let the People Speak!, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Media Organizations -- Light on the Bay, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Media Organizations -- Lockport Community Cable Commission, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Media Organizations -- Los Alamitos Television, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Media Organizations -- MADRE, 1991-1997 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Media Organizations -- Manhattan Neighborhood Network, 1992-1995 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Media Organizations -- Maryknoll World Productions, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Media Organizations -- Maryland Art Place, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Media Organizations -- Media Alliance, 1987-1995 (Box 63, Folder 22, Box 77, Folder 20)
  - Media Organizations -- Media Network, 1992-1994 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Media Organizations -- Michigan Cable Awareness Project, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Media Organizations -- Mid-Peninsula Peace Center, 1986-1987 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Media Organizations -- Migrant Media, London, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Media Organizations -- Milwaukee Access Telecommunications Authority, 1988-1991 (Box 64, Folder 4, Box 75, Folder 18)
  - Media Organizations -- Monona School/Community Cable, Undated (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Media Organizations -- Montgomery Community Television, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Media Organizations -- National Alliance of Media Arts Centers, 1991-1992 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Media Organizations -- National Alliance of Media Arts and Culture, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Media Organizations -- National Asian American Telecommunications Association, 1987-1996 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Media Organizations -- National Black Media Coalition, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Media Organizations -- National Black Programming Consortium, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Media Organizations -- National Alliance of Media Arts Centers, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Media Organizations -- National Campaign for Freedom of Expression, Undated (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Media Organizations -- The National Coalition of 100 Black Women, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Media Organizations -- National Community Network, 1992 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Media Organizations -- National Federation of Local Cable Programmers, 1984-1990 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Media Organizations -- National Network for Youth Media Distribution, 2000 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Media Organizations -- Network of Cultural Centers of Color, 1994-1995 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Media Organizations -- New Orleans Video Access Center, 1987-1990 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Media Organizations -- New York Citizens Committee for Responsible Media, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Media Organizations -- Nonprofit Computer Exchange, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Media Organizations -- Non-Profit Coordinating Committee of New York, 1993-1994 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Media Organizations -- NW Community Television, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Media Organizations -- Oakland County Cable Communications Corporation, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 24)
  - Media Organizations -- Open Channel TV Base, 1999 (Box 64, Folder 25)
  - Media Organizations -- Oxford Film and Video Makers, 1994 (Box 64, Folder 26)
  - Media Organizations -- Parabola Arts Foundation, Inc., 1987 (Box 64, Folder 27)
  - Media Organizations -- Pastors for Peace, 1993 (Box 64, Folder 28)
  - Media Organizations -- Peralta Colleges Television, 1987-1992 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Media Organizations -- El Pitirre Noticias Communidad Puertorriqueña/Latina, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Media Organizations -- Pittsburgh Filmmakers, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Media Organizations -- The Public Access Producers Academy, 1985 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Media Organizations -- The Public Telecommunications Newsletter, 1990 (Box 75, Folder 16)
  - Media Organizations -- Queens Public Access Television, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Media Organizations -- Reel New York, circa 1997 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Media Organizations -- The Rhode Island Community Television Network, 1988 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Media Organizations -- Rhode Island Laborvision, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Media Organizations -- Rise and Shine Productions, 1986-1994 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Media Organizations -- Saint Paul Neighborhood Network, 1997-2001 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Media Organizations -- SANKOFA, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Media Organizations -- The Scribe Video Center, 1990-1994 (Box 65, Folder 11, Box 77, Folder 22)
  - Media Organizations -- Small World, London, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Media Organizations -- Sommerville Community Access Television, 1988-1993 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Media Organizations -- Spectrum Communications, Undated (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Media Organizations -- Squeaky Wheel/Buffalo Media Resources, Inc., Undated (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Media Organizations -- Stadtwerkstatt TV, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  - Media Organizations -- Staten Island Disarmament Campaign Coalition, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  - Media Organizations -- Street-Level Youth Media, 1998 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  - Media Organizations -- Study Circles Resource Center, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  - Media Organizations -- Tampa Cable Television, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  - Media Organizations -- Theater of the Oppressed, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  - Media Organizations -- Third World Newsreel, 1990-1993 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  - Media Organizations -- Tucson Community Cable Corporation, 1987-1991 (Box 75, Folder 19)
  - Media Organizations -- Turning Tide Productions, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  - Media Organizations -- TV Anhembi, Undated (Box 65, Folder 24)
  - Media Organizations -- Twin Cities Public TV, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 25)
  - Media Organizations -- UCVideo, 1985-1987 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  - Media Organizations -- Union for Democratic Communications, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  - Media Organizations -- Union Producers and Programmers Network, 1985-1991 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  - Media Organizations -- United Youth Newspaper by Youth Force, 1989-1992 (Box 75, Folder 20)
  - Media Organizations -- Videazimut, Undated (Box 65, Folder 29)
  - Media Organizations -- Video-Active Productions, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  - Media Organizations -- Video Juku, 2001 (Box 65, Folder 31)
  - Media Organizations -- Video Paz, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  - Media Organizations -- Video Popular, 1993-1994 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  - Media Organizations -- Videoteca del Sur, circa 1992 (Box 65, Folder 34)
  - Media Organizations -- Volunteer Lawyers for the Arts, Undated (Box 65, Folder 35)
  - Media Organizations -- WAC-TV, Boston Community Access and Programming Foundation, 1987 (Box 65, Folder 36)
  - Media Organizations -- Western Front, 1994 (Box 65, Folder 37)
  - Media Organizations -- William Greaves Productions, Inc., 1989 (Box 65, Folder 38)
  - Media Organizations -- Winthrop Community Access Television, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 39)
  - Media Organizations -- Women Make Movies, circa 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 40)
  - Media Organizations -- Women's Institute for Freedom of the Press, 1986 (Box 65, Folder 41)
  - Media Organizations -- The Women's Media Center, 2007 (Box 65, Folder 42)
  - Media Organizations -- World African Network, 1995 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Media Organizations -- WYBE-TV 35, Philadelphia, 1990-1992 (Box 66, Folder 2, Box 77, Folder 23)
  - Media Organizations -- Youth Force of the Citizens Committee for New York City, Inc., 1992 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Research Files -- Advertising, 1984-1986 (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - Research Files -- African and African American Programming, 1991-1994 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Research Files -- AIDS Research Funding, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Research Files -- Americanization and Consumption, circa 1978 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Research Files -- Asian Programming, 1991-1993 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Research Files -- Black History (U.S.), 1990-1994 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Research Files -- Bush Administration, 2005 (Box 193, Folder 8, 9)
  - Research Files -- Camp Casey, 2005; cuid39664 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_370)
    This file includes two short films: "Skipping in Camp Casey" by Chun Pan and "Camp Casey" by Sally Marr and Peter Dudar.
  - Research Files -- Chicana History, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Research Files -- C.I.A., 1980-1985 (Box 66, Folder 10, Box 194, Folder 9)
  - Research Files -- Cold War, 1986 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Research Files -- Colombian Human Rights Advocacy, 1997-1998 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Research Files -- Columbus Quincentenary, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Research Files -- Computer Networking Resources, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Research Files -- Constitutional RIghts, 1987-1996 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Research Files -- Copyright Law, 1991-1992 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  - Research Files -- Crime and Poverty, 1993 (Box 77, Folder 24)
  - Research Files -- Criminalization of Youth, 1992-1996 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  - Research Files -- Education as Crime Prevention, 1997 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  - Research Files -- Electoral Politics, 1987-1993 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  - Research Files -- Environmental Justice, 1989-1993 (Box 66, Folder 20, Box 194, Folder 10)
  - Research Files -- Federal Commission Policy, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 21)
  - Research Files -- Film Reviews, 1989-1992 (Box 66, Folder 22)
  - Research Files -- Georgia State Prison Strike, 2010; cuid39659 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_356)
  - Research Files -- Gulf War, 1991 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  - Research Files -- Haitian Coup and the Bush Administration, 2004 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  - Research Files -- Harriet Tubman - Fannie Lou Hamer Collective, 1990 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  - Research Files -- Healthcare and the United States Economy, 1993 (Box 194, Folder 11)
  - Research Files -- Housing, 1990-1994 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Research Files -- Hurricane Katrina, 2005 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Research Files -- Immigration in Germany, 2011; cuid39660 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_357)
  - Research Files -- Immigration Law (U.S.), 2003 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Research Files -- Indigenous Programming, 1992-1996 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Research Files -- Information Technology Policy (U.S.), 1980-1995 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Research Files -- Iraq History, 2004; cuid39661 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_358)
  - Research Files -- Iraq War, 2008-2009 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Research Files -- Israel-Palestine Conflict, 1990-2011; cuid39656 (Box 67, Folder 7, Box 77, Folder 25, Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_359)
  - Research Files -- Kensington Welfare Rights Union, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Research Files -- Latino Programming, 1993-1997 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Research Files -- Linguistic White Supremacy and the English-Only Movement (U.S.), 1987 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Research Files -- Local Athletic and Educational Courses, New York City, 1991-1993 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Research Files -- Local Television News, 1994 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - Research Files -- Magazine Publishing Industry (U.S.), 1982-1985 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Research Files -- Media Censorship, 1989-1992 (Box 67, Folder 14, Box 77, Folder 26)
  - Research Files -- Media Democratization, 1991-1996 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Research Files -- Media Influence on Culture, 1984-1999 (Box 67, Folder 16, Box 77, Folder 27, Box 194, Folder 12)
  - Research Files -- Media, Race, and Culture, 1982-1994 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Research Files -- National Information Infrastructure, 1986-1995 (Box 68, Folder 1, 2, 3)
  - Research Files -- New York City Local Activism, 1990-1998 (Box 68, Folder 4, Box 77, Folder 28)
  - Research Files -- News References, 2011; cuid39662 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_360)
  - Research Files -- Nicaraguan Elections and Contra War, 1987-1990 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Research Files -- Notebook of Press Clippings on the Gulf War, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Research Files -- Omnibus Crime Bill, 1993-1994 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Research Files -- RBS Funding Standards, 1990 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Research Files -- Peace Media Activism, 1981-1991 (Box 69, Folder 1, Box 75, Folder 21)
  - Research Files -- Pico Korea Workers Struggle, 1990 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Research Files -- Police Brutality, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Research Files -- Prison Industrial Complex, 1990-1999 (Box 69, Folder 4, 5, Box 77, Folder 29)
  - Research Files -- Prison Industrial Complex -- Television Representation, circa 1995 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Research Files -- Prison Privatization, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Research Files -- Public Access Television, 1980-1994 (Box 69, Folder 8, Box 75, Folder 22)
  - Research Files -- Public Service Advertising, 1996 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Research Files -- Racism in the United States, 1989-2005 (Box 69, Folder 10, Box 194, Folder 13)
  - Research Files -- Reproductive Health, 1991 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Research Files -- Rodney King Assault and Trial, 1993 (Box 194, Folder 14)
  - Research Files -- Satellite Technology, 1980-1994 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Research Files -- Save the Audobon Coalition, circa 1990 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Research Files -- South African Politics and Apartheid, 1993 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - Research Files -- Sweatshops, 1996-1999 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Research Files -- United Farm Workers of America, 1990-1992 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Research Files -- U.S. Treatment of Journalists in the Iraq War, 2003-2004 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Research Files -- Video Dial Tone, 1992-1994 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Research Files -- Video News Releases, 1992-1994 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Research Files -- War on Drugs, 1997-2001 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Research Files -- WikiLeaks, 2010; cuid39663 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_312_ER_361)
  - Research Files -- Women's Rights and Media Representation, 1995-1996 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Research Files -- World Conference on Women, Beijing, 1995 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Research Files -- Zapatista Movement, 2001 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Archived Websites, March 2009 - March 2021; 8 websites in 8 archived websites.
  Appraisal
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored with the permission of the content owner.
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of deepdishtv.org/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  This series contains websites and projects related to Deep Dish TV.
  Waves of Change: The Many Voices of the Global Village is a multimedia project by Deep Dish Network designed to survey community media around the world by compiling and archiving the creative use of participatory communication globally. Waves of Change acts as a platform to share pieces that do not get seen outside of local coverage. The website includes an interactive map individual projects from their location on a world map and other media. Uprooted was a multiplatform (web, tv, dvd) media tool for activists and organizers advocating for migrant rights. The website contains a blog, news and events, and project videos.
  We Interrupt this Program was a video/web series with Paper Tiger Television on the global eco-economic-political crises and rise in far-right politics. The series also includes a catalogue of all of their programs and associated video, as well as news, events, and other projects.
  In 2020, the Deep Dish TV website was revived and ransitioned from a non-profit organization producing and distributing progressive video to an archival swebite that contains over 500 hours of programming. The series also contains the older version of the Deep Dish TV website with video and descriptions.